Let's talk about this. Honestly, it really depends on
the size of your data. For small amounts of
binary data, very, very small amounts of binary data,
you could actually put the raw data in the
database. There are blob types and those are supported
and work pretty well. However, as you start putting
larger data into the database, it gets pretty inefficient.
And you end up writing a lot more code.
Well, as far as storing the files in a public folder
on the device is concerned, well, that might work if you
actually wanted to share those files. But, typically, you don't want to
share those files with other applications. So, storing them in a
public folder on the device isn't a very good idea. But
the third option is pretty good. Storing the files in a
private folder and then referencing the location in the database. Now,
admittedly, you might not even need to put them into the database
at all. But it's often nice to do this if
you need to do any kind of queries on them. You
can store metadata in the database and store files in
a private folder. This is what Android does in the gallery.